[{"id": "5cefc0c4948005ec986edcdf", "question": "Who is the sixth member of the group LOONA to debut?", "answer": "Kim Lip", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc87", "question": "What's the \"safest\" color on the US Homeland Security Advisory System's color scale?", "answer": "Green", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c055", "question": "Which bird is the national bird of Iran?", "answer": "Common nightingale", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a766", "question": "In which US state is Oral Roberts University located?", "answer": "Oklahoma", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe7c1e4877e98cb97778980", "question": "Where can you find the world's oldest lake?", "answer": "Siberia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59e6bba0fb6c85e9e634ff57", "question": "Managua is the capital of which Central American country?", "answer": "Nicaragua", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bac5", "question": "What year was National Geographic magazine first published?", "answer": "1888", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133998c", "question": "What actor provides the voice for  Sideshow Bob on the TV show \"The Simpsons\"?", "answer": "Kelsey Grammer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339de6", "question": "What seminal L.A. punk band was discovered by Ray Manzarek of the Doors?", "answer": "X", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399f2", "question": "Who is the lead guitarist in the band \"The Who\"?", "answer": "Pete Townsend", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fef5cfe6ce05a3942286e28", "question": "Which iconic \u201880s role required training from a professional mime?", "answer": "\"Robocop\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133acf2", "question": "What was the official name for the World War II evacuation of Dunkirk?", "answer": "Operation Dynamo", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b50a", "question": "How many squares are there on a Snakes and Ladders board?", "answer": "100", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fede30d6ce05a3942286dd0", "question": "Who originally sang \"Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer\"?", "answer": "Gene Autry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5be5809f5415ba52ed6f0ab6", "question": "What document is typically needed for one to enter a foreign country?", "answer": "A passport", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600cc3296de0eb824d4052eb", "question": "Which American city is considered to be the birthplace of blues music?", "answer": "Memphis, Tennessee -- In 1977, the U.S. Congress declared Beale Street to be the official \"Home of the Blues\".", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fde49fec6c6b019850c9a71", "question": "Which two nations fought for control of North America in the French and Indian War?", "answer": "France and England", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b807", "question": "What does 3 dots, 3 dashes, 3 dots mean in Morse Code?", "answer": "SOS", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6000ed209a72b906b34e3ce9", "question": "Fissures, vents and plugs are all associated with which geological feature?", "answer": "Volcano", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e40", "question": "What was the real name of TV's \"Mr. WIzard\"?", "answer": "Don Herbert", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a9e96e47ccba3ffe45786f3", "question": "A 25 to 31 mph wind on the Beaufort scale is called what?", "answer": "Strong breeze", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a144", "question": "Who is Scooby Doo's nephew??", "answer": "Scrappy Doo", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5ae", "question": "How many bits are there in a byte?", "answer": "8", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c695", "question": "The scientific unit named for Sir Isaac Newton measures what?", "answer": "Force", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59c1cdfe7bd84c0ea43ad432", "question": "Which city is directly northwest of Windsor, Ontario?", "answer": "Detroit", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d17", "question": "What newspaper editor wrote the headline \"Spider-Man: Threat or Menace\"?", "answer": "J. Jonah Jameson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dc2", "question": "What double-word song title was a hit single by Amy Grant?", "answer": "Baby Baby", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015f14afe83fe1f2a824c16", "question": "What ancient astrological event is December 25th also associated with?", "answer": "December 25 was the date of the winter solstice on the Roman calendar.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bc7", "question": "In which fictional Texas town did Beavis and Butthead live?", "answer": "Highland", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59e6b4abfb6c85e9e634ff44", "question": "What is a shark's skeleton made of?", "answer": "Cartilage", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392cf", "question": "What film stars Bruce Willis as a plastic surgeon Ernest Menville?", "answer": "Death Becomes Her", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f8b", "question": "What major God shares the same name in both Greek and Roman mythology?", "answer": "Apollo", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5a728c4c6bcd28c119383284", "question": "What reference book went on sale for the first time in 1955?", "answer": "The Guinness Book of Records", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe4b40906d333868d34d6de", "question": "What part of the world did the Vikings come from?", "answer": "Scandinavia", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad05", "question": "Where were the 1996 Summer Olympics held?", "answer": "Atlanta, Georgia", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f53", "question": "Who is Dinah, whom Alice thinks about nostalgically as she falls down the rabbit hole to Wonderland?", "answer": "Her cat", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe4b6b006d333868d34d6f3", "question": "In 1908, what three letters became recognized as the universal distress signal?", "answer": "SOS", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a22", "question": "What movie features the following line \"This war talk\u2019s spoiling all the fun at every party this spring\"?", "answer": "Gone with the Wind", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa4d", "question": "What is the capital of Portugal?", "answer": "Lisbon", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a50b", "question": "Lombard Street in London is the equivalent to which famous street in the US?", "answer": "Wall Street", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fe2", "question": "What is the name of Lois Lane's younger sister?", "answer": "Lucy Lane", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339959", "question": "Who played Frankenstein\u2019s monster in the 1931 movie \"Frankenstein\"?", "answer": "Boris Karloff", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b097", "question": "In what decade was NATO formed?", "answer": "1940s", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393d0", "question": "How many guns does Travis buy in the movie \"Taxi Driver\"?", "answer": "4", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338898", "question": "What two girls do Archie and Reggie run around with?", "answer": "Betty and Veronica", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a37a", "question": "What is the capital of Portugal?", "answer": "Lisbon", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "600781b5bd51d85e222ab64e", "question": "The marble slab that eventually became Michelangelo's David was originally intended as a statue of what famous character?", "answer": "The marble slab originally belonged to an artist named Agostino di Duccio, who planned to turn it into a statue of\u00a0Hercules.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399a4", "question": "What musical instrument is Woody Allen proficient at?", "answer": "Clarinet", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdd5d0a0499cffc60b84230", "question": "Who led the Solidarity movement and became President of Poland in 1990?", "answer": "Lech Walesa", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fef32ea6ce05a3942286dff", "question": "How many U.S. states are needed to ratify an amendment for it to become part of the constitution?", "answer": "Three-fourths", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c1c", "question": "Who voiced Cinderella in the 1950 Disney movie by the same name?", "answer": "Ilene Woods", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133974d", "question": "What is Alecia Moore better known as?", "answer": "P!NK", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600242374be4723ccac22182", "question": "Which leading English poet of was killed in action during World War I one week before the end of the war?", "answer": "Wilfred Owen", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a90", "question": "Dr. Brown's puppy in \"Back to the Future Part II\" was named after what astronomer?", "answer": "Copernicus", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c52f", "question": "What is the nearest star to Earth?", "answer": "The Sun", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0fb", "question": "Marvin Lee Aday is the real name of which well known singer?", "answer": "Meatloaf", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a864", "question": "What is the literal translation of Montenegro's name?", "answer": "Black mountain", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133997c", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", what is Krusty the Clown's real full name?", "answer": "Herschel Shmoikel Pinchas Yerucham Krustofsky", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "591c3512815febcc896f9259", "question": "In which country would you find the motor racing circuit called Kyalami?", "answer": "South Africa", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b92d", "question": "What game has the winner striking the loser's wrist with two extended fingers?", "answer": "Rock, Paper, Scissors", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c986", "question": "The Big Dipper is part of what constellation?", "answer": "Ursa Major", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ffcfdbb9dc5ec6cd98a8325", "question": "What novel is set on a desert planet inhabited by giant sandworms?", "answer": "Dune", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fea3923ff048f679a45ab27", "question": "The metamorphism of what rock forms marble?", "answer": "Limestone", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc5f", "question": "What material are jeans made of?", "answer": "Cotton", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59a1a1e512f2a7826b9b8716", "question": "What was the name given to the French goverment which collaborated with the Nazis?", "answer": "Vichy", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd6e", "question": "The most traditional Greek feta cheese is made from what animal's milk?", "answer": "Sheep's milk", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5ea", "question": "What designer introduced the miniskirt in 1965?", "answer": "Mary Quant", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b29e", "question": "What sports event did Rosie Ruiz win by cheating in 1980?", "answer": "The Boston Marathon", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fd9696a23c87fd04dd15e09", "question": "Which historical military commander was never defeated?", "answer": "Alexander the Great", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c88f", "question": "What does the Kelvin scale measure?", "answer": "Temperature", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6015fcddfe83fe1f2a824c46", "question": "Which scientist patented new ballet shoes to protect dancers\u2019 feet?", "answer": "Bill Nye", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe25860658e585fda9cfa3f", "question": "Ceviche is made by marinating raw fish in what type of liquid?", "answer": "Lime juice", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe4de4c06d333868d34d712", "question": "Octavian defeated Mark Anthony in which famous naval battle of 31 B.C.?", "answer": "The Battle of Actium", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58b0e916964118b2bb3809ca", "question": "What did Esther Howland popularize in the US?", "answer": "Valentine\u2019s Day greeting cards", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8d1", "question": "What sport was played by the Brooklyn Dodgers?", "answer": "Baseball", "category": "general"}, {"id": "601b4c3049076251badbeacf", "question": "Which unique pet did Calvin Coolidge have during his presidency?", "answer": "Raccoon -- Named Rachel, she might be the most well known pet.  She walked around on a leash and was the master of mischief.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0b0", "question": "Which fictional park is the home of Yogi Bear?", "answer": "Jellystone", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59067a2dff9c0647b50a8055", "question": "Which Japanese company manufactured the final videocassette recorder on July 22, 2016?", "answer": "Funai", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c35b", "question": "How many feet do snails have?", "answer": "One", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8c9", "question": "Until 1790, what was known as Jenkins Hill?", "answer": "Capitol Hill", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b02a", "question": "What ousted Eastern European leader was executed on Christmas Day in 1989?", "answer": "Nicolae Ceausescu", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5906823cff9c0647b50a809b", "question": "Which NFL team won Super Bowl 50?", "answer": "Denver Broncos", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a63e", "question": "Which US state is home to the Odessa Crater?", "answer": "Texas", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fd2cff32596a59cbdfbd375", "question": "Who said, \"Nearly all men can stand adversity, but if you want to test a man's character, give him power\"?", "answer": "Abraham Lincoln", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59008c40cf842fa4c4ba969e", "question": "With which horror film series would you associate the character Leatherface?", "answer": "Texas Chainsaw Massacre", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe9f1eaff048f679a45aab3", "question": "Insect bodies have how many major divisions?", "answer": "Three", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d66", "question": "Who played the role of TV's D. J. Tanner?", "answer": "Candace Cameron", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5febda227e83c707845b2181", "question": "Which American golfer was nicknamed \"The Joplin Ghost\"?", "answer": "Horton Smith", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e1", "question": "What is the name of the first book in the \"Bourne Trilogy\"?", "answer": "The Bourne Identity", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a759", "question": "What is Alaska's largest lake?", "answer": "Iliamna Lake", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "600f6e88a9e54d890926f6c6", "question": "Which two islands makes up a commonwealth with Antigua?", "answer": "Barbuda and Redonda -- The three-island nation is in the Lesser Antilles.  Redondo is uninhabited and was formed from a volcano.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59067b19ff9c0647b50a8060", "question": "The Gotthard Base Tunnel, which opened on June 1, 2016, is located in which country?", "answer": "Switzerland", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3f0", "question": "In which hemisphere is the Tropic of Cancer located?", "answer": "Northern", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a653", "question": "Which US state is nickname the \"Palmetto State\"?", "answer": "South Carolina", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395f4", "question": "In The Simpsons, what sits next to the basement door in the Simpson's house?", "answer": "Grandfather clock", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c95", "question": "What TV show takes place in the fictional city of Capeside, Massachusetts?", "answer": "Dawson's Creek", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339690", "question": "What is the name of King Arthur's sidekick in the 1975 movie \"Monty Python and the Holy Grail\"?", "answer": "Patsy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c09e", "question": "How many gallons does a \"half butt\" barrel contain?", "answer": "63", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf59", "question": "Who wrote the mIRC chat software?", "answer": "Khaled Mardam-Bey", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b193", "question": "What year did Napoleon become the Emperor of the French?", "answer": "1804", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5a899c2e60d398dc9cf7a6a5", "question": "Vesta is the Roman goddess of what?", "answer": "Hearth, home and family", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59524521736d4be723796b6b", "question": "What French impressionist painter died in 1926", "answer": "Claude Monet", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5af98753aeb0982ee4559553", "question": "What is believed to be the first political cartoon published in colonial America?", "answer": "Join or Die Cartoon", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133941d", "question": "What album was the first to have all of its tracks licensed for use in movies, TV shows and commercials?", "answer": "\"Play\" by Moby", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b517", "question": "What is the only alcoholic drink one can buy in the dry Moore county in Tennessee?", "answer": "Jack Daniel's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5ef", "question": "How does a beaver signal to other beavers that danger is present?", "answer": "Slaps its tail on the water", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b743", "question": "What is known as the \"Mary Celeste\"?", "answer": "A ship", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd6a00d6c0f9723ab15cb32", "question": "What year was the first black hole discovered?", "answer": "1971", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bd2", "question": "Who designed Richard Gere's wardrobe in the movie \"American Gigolo\"?", "answer": "Giorgio Armani", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cb7", "question": "What TV show featured the fictional \"The Cobra Lodge\" fraternity?", "answer": "Mama's Family", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bab", "question": "Which book begins with the words \"The scent and smoke and sweat of a casino are nauseating at three in the morning\"?", "answer": "Casino Royale", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397e7", "question": "Which film mogul was famous for illogical sayings such as \"include me out\"?", "answer": "Sam Goldwyn", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff2102531a458464a93c43c", "question": "What classic novel was originally published with the title \"Fiesta\" in the U.K.?", "answer": "\"The Sun Also Rises", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fea4241ff048f679a45ab77", "question": "What is the opening of a camera lens, which controls the amount of light?", "answer": "Aperture", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ead", "question": "What screen legend made his final appearance in the movie \"The Score\"?", "answer": "Marlon Brando", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a25f2616682715b82711cea", "question": "Which Canadian city is know as \"Steeltown\"?", "answer": "Hamilton, Ontario", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae46", "question": "What acclaimed novelist was a war correspondent during the Spanish Civil War and World War II?", "answer": "Ernest Hemingway", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338996", "question": "Who wrote the novel \"Terms of Endearment\" that was later adapted into a 1983 Best Picture film?", "answer": "Larry McMurtry", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe73405eec85e375820b22b", "question": "How old was the youngest American serviceman in World War II?", "answer": "12", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390ce", "question": "Turnov, Rusty and Bobo appear in what stage musical?", "answer": "Starlight Express", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe9005501dd7bf43be5e866", "question": "How many US gallons is in a barrel of oil?", "answer": "42", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5c90d50252800b05cac20f1c", "question": "What year did Tom Hanks win the Best Actor Oscar for his role in the film \"Philadelphia\"?", "answer": "1993", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1e6", "question": "Which US president lived in Shadow Lawn?", "answer": "Woodrow Wilson", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388d7", "question": "In Norse mythology, what was the name of the monster killed by Beowulf?", "answer": "Grendel", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339227", "question": "What decade did Marty McFly go back to in \"Back to the Future\"?", "answer": "1950's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf0d", "question": " What month does the summer solstice occur in the northern hemisphere?", "answer": "June", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea8078ff048f679a45ac19", "question": "What extinct animal was the ancestor of cattle?", "answer": "Auroch", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b830", "question": "What is the device that measures the number of steps you take when walking or running?", "answer": "Pedometer", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c9df", "question": "Which branch of science is concerned with the study of matter and energy?", "answer": "Physics", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe6990f20565ad31a57c740", "question": "What legendary athlete lit the Olympic torch at the 1996 Atlanta Olympics?", "answer": "Mohammed Ali", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b936", "question": "What is  the first possible property purchase on Monopoly?", "answer": "Baltic Avenue", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c346", "question": "What fluid was the chemical \"taurine\" first derived from?", "answer": "Ox bile", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae08", "question": "Which New England state was an independent republic for 14 years before joining the union?", "answer": "Vermont", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca77", "question": "An imperial fathom has how many yards?", "answer": "2", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388fe", "question": "What musical is set in the fictional English town of Everington?", "answer": "Billy Elliot", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133951a", "question": "Who voiced Hades in the 1997 Disney movie \"Hercules\"?", "answer": "James Woods", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5e93a613d6f11f394a3b2d54", "question": "What is the name of the Air company in the movie \"The Lorax\"?", "answer": "O'Hare Air", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b55b", "question": "What is the term used for the science of growing an apple?", "answer": "Pomology", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf29", "question": "What sporting event first took place in 1903?", "answer": "Tour de France", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea3af5ff048f679a45ab30", "question": "What are the three-time periods of the dinosaurs?", "answer": "Triassic, Jurassic, and Cretaceous", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1e2", "question": "What year did Andre and Edouard Michelin first publish the \"Michelin Guide\"?", "answer": "1900", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bcb1", "question": "What kind of fruit juice is used to mix a Salty Dog?", "answer": "Grapefruit", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fecc262ec223966ae8f8874", "question": "What movie star uses his middle initial, B, for \"Bakari\", to avoid confusion with a retired basketball star?", "answer": "Michael B. Jordan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe0de8bfcbed638185eaa16", "question": "In which US state is Crater Lake found?", "answer": "Oregon", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "590679b0ff9c0647b50a8050", "question": "On January 1, 2016, which Canadian province became the first one to allow the testing of self-driving vehicles on public roads?", "answer": "Ontario", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59008851cf842fa4c4ba9688", "question": "In which country is the Commandaria wine region?", "answer": "Cyprus", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a66d", "question": "What US city is known as the \"Biggest Little City in the World\"?", "answer": "Reno", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133acd9", "question": "Which president had a swimming pool installed in the White House?", "answer": "Franklin Roosevelt", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c483", "question": "In what decade was the very first test-tube baby born?", "answer": "1970s", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9de", "question": "Bubble Wrap was invented while researchers were trying to make what?", "answer": "Wallpaper", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b0d", "question": "In the Tom Petty song \"Free Fallin'\", the girl is a big fan of what singer?", "answer": "Elvis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bf2", "question": "In which city was the composer Ludwig Van Beethoven born?", "answer": "Bonn", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa8d", "question": "Dakar is the capital of which African country?", "answer": "Senegal", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7f7", "question": "The electric eel is native only to what continent?", "answer": "South America", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c893", "question": "What does the Schmidt index measure?", "answer": "Pain of insect stings", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d6b", "question": "What Canadian actor's 1999 memoir was entitled \"Get a Life\"?", "answer": "William Shatner's", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ffa40e0c73aa70ea0b70b0b", "question": "Which U.S. state claims to be the diner capital of the world?", "answer": "New Jersey", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e2b", "question": "Who is Jamie Lee Curtis' mother?", "answer": "Janet Leigh", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a103", "question": "Directed by Sydney Pollack, which film won the Oscar for Best Picture in 1986?", "answer": "Out of Africa", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be3b", "question": "How many players are there in a standard polo team?", "answer": "Four", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fecd118ec223966ae8f88bd", "question": "In the 2015 movie, \"Ant-Man\", what hero disappears into a subatomic quantum realm while disabling a Soviet nuclear missile?", "answer": "Wasp", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fe5", "question": "What actress wrote the autobiography \"Call Me Anna\"?", "answer": "Patty Duke", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a107", "question": "\"Eyes Wide Shut\" was the last film of which director?", "answer": "Stanley Kubrick", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f23", "question": "Which Old Master signed his paintings with his full Cretan name, Dom\u00e9nikos Theotok\u00f3poulos?", "answer": "El Greco", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6015f61ffe83fe1f2a824c1b", "question": "In 1919, 21 people were killed in Boston due to a flood of what?", "answer": "Molasses", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6010c5a40775fa611bce67ca", "question": "The spice paprika is made from what?", "answer": "Sweet pepper pods -- Paprika is made from ground sweet pepper pods that are dried and powdered.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad9d", "question": "In what city did Rosa Parks refuse to give up her seat for a white passenger?", "answer": "Montgomery, Alabama", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59a552373e1c6f9840ba3193", "question": "What color flag indicates a fair throw in the shot put?", "answer": "White", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c303", "question": "Which media is read from the outside in, compact discs or vinyl records?", "answer": "Vinyl records", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe937986bd93ce3a4e5f671", "question": "Dystychiphobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Accidents", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be1a", "question": "What word did the University of Hawaii Warriors drop from their team name in 2001?", "answer": "Rainbow", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388a2", "question": "What forest was home to Robin Hood?", "answer": "The Sherwood Forest", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9bb", "question": "The zodiac sign \"Capricorn\" refers to what animal?", "answer": "The goat", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bae2", "question": "How many candles are on a menorah?", "answer": "9", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392b5", "question": "Which French fashion designer created the conical bra for Madonna's \"Blond Ambition\" tour?", "answer": "Jean-Paul Gaultier", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7b7", "question": "In which US state are the Catskill Mountains located?", "answer": "New York", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397bd", "question": "What Broadway soundtrack was the best selling album of the 1960's?", "answer": "West Side Story", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd57", "question": "The Pritzker Prize is an award given in what field?", "answer": "Architecture", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339804", "question": "What movie soundtrack is Eric Clapton's \"Tears in Heaven\" from?", "answer": "Rush", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5b3", "question": "How many times can you fold a regular piece of paper in half?", "answer": "7", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a297", "question": "What was the name of Phil Collins' first solo album?", "answer": "Face Value", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133926c", "question": "How many colors are there in a rainbow?", "answer": "Seven", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58f166fbf7c52aae91cc07b4", "question": "Which is the largest of Neptune's moons?", "answer": "Triton", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7e3", "question": "What letter in the alphabet is the only one with more than one syllable?", "answer": "W", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59067e76ff9c0647b50a807a", "question": "Who was awarded the 2016 Nobel Prize for Literature?", "answer": "Bob Dylan", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6015ec8bfe83fe1f2a824c04", "question": "How many Jews did the real-life Oskar Schindler save during the Holocaust?", "answer": "1200", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a08e", "question": "Who portrayed Han Solo in the Star Wars film series?", "answer": "Harrison Ford", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab49", "question": "Which ocean does Somalia has water access to?", "answer": "Indian", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ad7e7bcb24f84e0b9f9ffbd", "question": "How many Federal territories are part of Australia?", "answer": "Ten", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc17", "question": "What organization was formed to replace \"The League of Nations\"?", "answer": "United Nations", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388f1", "question": "What Agatha Christie novel was made up of two parts - England and Egypt?", "answer": "Death on the Nile", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5af258dfb63e5727cf5a4849", "question": "Who sang the 1995 song \"Boom Boom Boom\"?", "answer": "The Outhere Brothers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbd8", "question": "What typewriter key was introduced by Remington in 1878, ending the need for two keys for each letter?", "answer": "Shift key", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e27", "question": "Who is Liza Minnelli's mother?", "answer": "Judy Garland", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5e94cf395ea27d7a1303aece", "question": "Which rapper went platinum with his 2014 Album \"2014 Forest Hills Drive\"?", "answer": "J. Cole", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ae860a84007905755f79e8f", "question": "What year was Julius Caeser assassinated", "answer": "44 BC", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a565", "question": "Which US state is home to the Pebble Beach Golf Links?", "answer": "California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59e804ffde59ea584496fea8", "question": "Archie Moore is typically associated with which sport?", "answer": "Boxing", "category": "general"}, {"id": "601b4a7649076251badbeab6", "question": "Who patented the concept of a flat engine in 1896?", "answer": "Karl Benz", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9ee", "question": "What event occurs at Walthamstow Stadium?", "answer": "Greyhound Racing", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ffb58155dad637d903c880e", "question": "Venice's famed Bridge of Sighs connects two what?", "answer": "Prisons -- The bridge connects an old prison inside the Doge's Palace to a newer one across the Rio di Palazzo.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c395", "question": "What prevents the Earth's atmosphere from drifting into space?", "answer": "Gravity", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c238", "question": "What did Harry Houdini die from on Halloween in 1926?", "answer": "Ruptured appendix", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd37", "question": "Who scored the famous \"Hand of God\" goal in the 1986 World Cup?", "answer": "Diego Maradona", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe8a91b01dd7bf43be5e747", "question": "What type of vegetarian excludes all types of meat from their diet but eats eggs and dairy products?", "answer": "A lacto-ovo vegetarian", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4f3", "question": "Where is the Sea of Tranquility?", "answer": "The Moon", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c237", "question": "What are the two traditional colors of Halloween?", "answer": "Orange and black", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad98", "question": "When was John F. Kennedy assassinated?", "answer": "November 22, 1963", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8e4", "question": "What did Henry Shrapnel invent?", "answer": "Exploding shell", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c78a", "question": "What is the chemical formula for ozone?", "answer": "O3", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c34f", "question": "What shape is the body of an Erlenmeyer flask?", "answer": "Conical", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1d0", "question": "What star of \"The Breakfast Club\" was also part of the cast of the TV show \"The Facts of Life\"?", "answer": "Molly Ringwald", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59f9b9bd364247bf200fb890", "question": "What kind of bones once stiffened corsets?", "answer": "Whale", "category": "general"}, {"id": "601b4b4549076251badbeac1", "question": "Who was the first female U.S. Attorney General?", "answer": "Janet Reno -- She served as the attorney general for President Bill Clinton's entire presidency.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7d7", "question": "Luzon and Mindanao are the two largest islands of what country?", "answer": "The Philippines", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "594d08241a1c922dd1ac64c0", "question": "Ulaanbaatar is the capital of which Asian country?", "answer": "Mongolia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6008ddb0f4f3bc4a292f8623", "question": "After World War II, who was the first leader of the Socialist Federal Republic of Yugoslavia?", "answer": "Ivan Ribar (From December 29. 2945 until January 14, 1953, he was the President of the Federal Assembly of Yugoslavia.)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "60078566bd51d85e222ab65e", "question": "Who said: \"I\u2019m the president of the United States, and I\u2019m not going to eat any more broccoli\"?", "answer": "George H.W. Bush (He once made a joke that the workers in the Office of Personnel Management would get merit pay \"in broccoli\").", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0bf", "question": "What was the screen name of the lead character in the TV show \"The Untouchables\"?", "answer": "Elliot", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c8b", "question": "What was Tom Clancy\u2019s first novel, publisher in 1984?", "answer": "The Hunt for Red October", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b349", "question": "Who was the first woman to sail single-handed around the world?", "answer": "Naomi James", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bafa", "question": "What billionaire once owned Las Vegas' Desert Inn, The Sands, The Frontier, and Castaways?", "answer": "Howard Hughes", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abb2", "question": "What US state has a Thames River?", "answer": "Connecticut", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc06", "question": "A crusiverbalist is someone who is skilled at what?", "answer": "The creation or solving of crosswords", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5e147a756ca6dac04a20ca4f", "question": "When did Thomas Jefferson purchase the territory of Louisiana?", "answer": "1803", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e37", "question": "What children's classic first chapter is titled \"Up the Mountain to Alm-Uncle\"?", "answer": "Heidi", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a2d", "question": "What does Peppermint Patty always call Charlie Brown in the \"Peanuts\" cartoon strip?", "answer": "Chuck", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58d116db4fea7fe947a22273", "question": "From what Gaelic word is \"Dublin\" derived?", "answer": "Dublind", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fd18b4a29d03ab85b632b30", "question": "What is a male turkey called?", "answer": "Tom", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58d117a64fea7fe947a2227b", "question": "Which Englishman was famously beheaded on October 29th, 1618?", "answer": "Walter Raleigh", "category": "history"}, {"id": "597cdb6ee347d002c297e4dd", "question": "What does the energiser bunny wear on his feet?", "answer": "Flip flops", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "60136fc1138175489539637b", "question": "What item gives the Green Lantern his power?", "answer": "Ring -- Turns out the key to being one of the most powerful superheroes in the DC universe is the ability to accessorize.", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7352deec85e375820b246", "question": "Who was President Nixon's first vice president?", "answer": "Spiro T. Agnew", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a94d", "question": "What two \"Great\" lakes are the largest two lakes entirely within Canada?", "answer": "Great Bear and Great Slave lakes", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5b3231d3bf195a31e15d7388", "question": "Also known as the \"Chile Pine\", what is the common name of the tree \"Araucaria araucana\"?", "answer": "Monkey puzzle", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5f7", "question": "What gender are whiptail lizards?", "answer": "Female", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392c8", "question": "Who authored the song \"In the Ghetto\"?", "answer": "Mac Davis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6f8", "question": "What Olympic field event's two main styles are the glide and the spin?", "answer": "Shot put's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a553", "question": "Which three US states have shorelines along Lake Superior?", "answer": "Michigan, Minnesota, Wisconsin", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391ff", "question": "What was The Police's biggest selling single?", "answer": "Every Breath You Take", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe9f507ff048f679a45aad0", "question": "Necrophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Death and dead things", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be07", "question": "Frank Sinatra was buried with a bottle of what whiskey?", "answer": "Jack Daniel's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59008fc3cf842fa4c4ba96c0", "question": "Who wrote the epic poem \"Paradise Lost\"?", "answer": "John Milton", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5e8a60e49a45431f553a9ccd", "question": "What movie had the highest rating on IMDb in 2019?", "answer": "The Shawshank Redemption", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff0af89e662d71a53650fbf", "question": "A gold medal is awarded to the winner of which Pulitzer Prize category?", "answer": "Public Service", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5b7ff9513a3a814d89068c53", "question": "What is Ethiopia's official language?", "answer": "Amharic", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133979e", "question": "What Happy Day's star turned down the plum film role of Danny Zuko in \"Grease\"?", "answer": "Henry Winkler", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af2c", "question": "When did the Massacre of Glencoe occur?", "answer": "February 12 1692", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399f8", "question": "What was the subtitle of the 2005 movie \"Miss Congeniality 2\"?", "answer": "Armed and Fabulous", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b20e", "question": "Who was assassinated by James Earl Ray?", "answer": "Martin Luther King, Jr.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd99", "question": "How many points is the red inner circle on a dartboard bull's-eye worth?", "answer": "Fifty", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5937eeb208d98002fdd633d7", "question": "Who sang the hit song \"Confide in Me\" in 1994?", "answer": "Kylie Minogue", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133924a", "question": "What was the title of Eddie Murphy's first movie?", "answer": "48 Hrs", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe6a8ab20565ad31a57c7f9", "question": "What was on the first-ever 12-inch record?", "answer": "Beethoven's Fifth Symphony", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe3e91738e4e5d4832e630e", "question": "In the Bible in the book of Job, who begins the first discourse to Job?", "answer": "Eliphaz", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391a9", "question": "Who voices the character of scientist and inventor Professor John I.Q. Nerdelbaum Frink Jr. on \"The Simpsons\"?", "answer": "Hank Azaria", "category": "entertainment"}]